Finding Aid for the Tony Barrett Papers PASC.0061
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1. Television and motion picture scripts and production material
  - If Tomorrow Comes (ABC, 1971)
    - THE GLASS HAMMER by Lew Hunter, 1971 February 17 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - THE GLASS HAMMER by Lew Hunter, 1971 March 3 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - THE GLASS HAMMER by Lew Hunter, 1970 December 7 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - The Investigators (CBS, 1961)
    - THE FINE PRINT SPELLS DEATH by Tony Barrett, 1961-1968 (Box 85, Folder 7)
      Includes notes. Also includes pilot script for The Interrogator, "a television series based on the files of John E. Reid and Associates"; Paramount Pictures telephone directory, 1968 August.
    - SAFETY IN NUMBERS by Tony Barrett and Joel Murcott, 1961 (Box 85, Folder 8)
      Includes: notes; letter from Michael Garrison; WGA notice of writing credits for DEATH LEAVES A TIP, which was probably the broadcast title.
  - Ironside (NBC, 1967-1975)
    - EAT, DRINK, AND BE BURIED by Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 126, Folders 1-2)
    - Ideas, undated (Box 126, Folder 3)
      Also includes shooting schedule for DEAD MAN'S TALE, 1967 August 3.
    - EAT, DRINK, AND BE BURIED by Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - THE ONLY WAY TO BEAT THE HORSES IS WITH A STICK by Don M. Mankiewicz and Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - DEAD MAN'S TALE by Don M. Mankiewicz, Donald A. Brinkley, and Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - DEAD MAN'S TALE by Don M. Mankiewicz and Donald A. Brinkley, 1967 July 31 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - It Takes a Thief (ABC, 1968-1970)
    - Notes, undated (Box 99, Folders 1-2)
    - A MATTER OF GREY MATTER notes, undated (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - A MATTER OF GREY MATTER by Tony Barrett and Gene L. Coon, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - A MATTER OF ROYAL LARCENY notes and script pages by Tony Barrett, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - A MATTER OF GREY MATTER by Tony Barrett and Gene L. Coon from a story by Tony Barrett, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Jane Wyman Presents the Fireside Theatre (NBC, 1955-1958)
    - TEN PERCENT by Tony Barrett from a story by Ronn Marvin, 1956 May 2 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - PORTRAIT IN FEAR by Tony Barrett, 1956 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      Includes acting contract for Barrett.
    - TEN PERCENT by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Jericho (CBS, 1966-1967)
    - AN HONEST DAY'S WORK FOR A DISHONEST DOLLAR by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - AN HONEST DAY'S WORK FOR A DISHONEST DOLLAR by Tony Barrett, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - A LOYAL FRIEND OF THE ENEMY by Tony Barrett, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Notes and correspondence, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - FOUR O'CLOCK BOMB TO LONDON by Stanford Sherman, 1966 September 23 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - SMALL WAR ON THE RIVIERA by Alvin Boretz, 1966 September 1 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Johnny Nighthawk
    This was intended as a series but never got picked up. The pilot was aired as part of Adventure Showcase (CBS, 1959).
    - BIG Box FOR BASKERSVILLE, undated (Box 111, Folders 8-9)
    - BIG Box FOR BASKERSVILLE production notes, undated (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - LONG ARM OF DEATH, undated (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Outlines and notes, undated (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - FLIGHT INTO FEAR by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - SITTING DUCK by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - "The Component Parts of 'Johnny Nighthawk'" by Tony Barrett, 1957 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - FLIGHT INTO FEAR by Tony Barrett, 1956 November 12 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - SITTING DUCK by Tony Barrett, 1956 September 21 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - APPOINTMENT WITH DEATH by Tony Barrett, 1957 April 8 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - The Lineup (CBS, 1950-1953)
    - THE HARLAN CASE, 1955 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - A Man Called Shenandoah (ABC, 1965-1966)
    - Notes, undated (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - AN UNFAMILIAR TUNE by Theodore Apstein and Tony Barrett, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      Includes notes. Also includes THE LOST DIABLO by Samuel A. Peeples, 1965 November 24 and THE RILEY BRAND by Charles Hoffman, 1966 January 6.
    - AN UNFAMILIAR TUNE by Theodore Apstein and Tony Barrett, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - The Man from U.N.C.L.E. (NBC, 1964-1968)
    - THE DEADLY TOYS AFFAIR by Robert Hill, 1965 August 11 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Story ideas, undated (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - McCabe (unrealized)
    - Treatment for a one-hour television project by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Treatment by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Notes, undated (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - The Mod Squad (ABC, 1968-1973)
    - ... AND A LITTLE CHILD SHALL BLEED THEM by Steffi and Tony Barrett, 1971 (Box 1, Folders 1-5)
      Also includes casting material.
    - "A" IS FOR ANNIE by William Bast, 1970 June 17 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Production material, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - BAD MAN ON CAMPUS by Robert Heverly, 1968 (Box 2, Folders 1-2)
    - OH, SEE THE BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE by Margaret Armen and Don Ingalls, 1969 (Box 2, Folders 3-4)
    - ANOTHER FINAL GAME by Frank Telford, 1972 June 9 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - AND ONCE FOR MY BABY by Robert Sherman, 1972 November 14 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - CALL BACK YESTERDAY by Robert Malcolm Young and John W. Bloch, 1970 (Box 3, Folders 1-2)
    - A BUMMER FOR R.J. by Jack Turley, 1970 (Box 3, Folders 3, 4 and 6)
    - BELINDA - THE END OF LITTLE MISS BUBBLE GUM! by Bryn Morgan, 1972 September 12 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - CHILD OF SORROW, CHILD OF LIGHT by Cliff Gould, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - THE CAVE by Don Ingalls, 1971 (Box 4, Folders 2-3)
    - CAPTAIN GREER CALL SURGERY by Tony Lawrence, 1968 (Box 4, Folders 4-5)
    - CAN YOU HEAR ME OUT THERE?, 1972 August 30 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - THE COMEBACK by Mann Rubin, 1970 December 28 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - THE CONNECTION by Rick Husky, 1972 (Box 5, Folders 2-4)
    - COLOR OF LAUGHTER, COLOR OF TEARS by Edward J. Lasko, 1971 (Box 5, Folders 5-6)
    - CRICKET by Rick Husky, 1971 (Box 6, Folders 1-2, Box 7, Folder 1)
    - CORBEY by Jack Turley, 1972 (Box 6, Folders 3-5)
    - CONFRONTATION! by George Bellak, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - THE DEADLY SIN by Robert Malcolm Young, 1969 (Box 7, Folders 2-3)
    - CRIME CLUB by Theodore J. Flicker, 1972 (Box 7, Folders 4-6)
      Also includes production documents.
    - Unused dialogue, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - THE DEBT by Steffi and Tony Barrett, 1969 November 20 (Box 8, Folders 1-3)
    - THE DEATH OF WILD BILL HANNACHEK by Mark Saha, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - DEATH IN HIGH PLACES by Robert Hamner, 1972 (Box 8, Folders 5-6)
    - A DOUBLE FOR DANGER by Roger Hill Lewis, 1970 November 11 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - CHILD OF A CHILD by Margaret and Paul Schneider, 1972 (Box 9, Folders 2-4)
    - DOING THE THING IN SOULSVILLE by Robert L. Goodwin, 1968 August 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - THE DECISION by Robert Malcolm Young, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - EYES OF THE BEHOLDER by Steffi and Tony Barrett, 1972 (Box 10, Folders 1-3, Box 11, Folder 6)
    - AN EYE FOR AN EYE by Tony Barrett, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - EXIT THE CLOSER by Robert Collins, 1971 (Box 10, Folders 5-6)
    - THE EXILE by Don Richman and Harve Bennett, 1969 November 28 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - FEET OF CLAY by Don Ingalls, 1971 (Box 11, Folders 1-2)
    - FEAR IS THE BUCKING HORSE by Tony Barrett, 1968 (Box 11, Folders 3-4)
      Working title: A FAVOR FOR A FRIEND; also includes production documents.
    - A FAR AWAY PLACE SO NEAR by Theodore Apstein, 1970 July 3 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - THE FUR COAT OF DEATH by Gerald Sanford, 1972 (Box 12, Folders 1-2)
    - FLIGHT FIVE DOESN'T ANSWER by Harve Bennett, with story by Stephen Kandel, 1968 November 13 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - FIND TARA CHAPMAN! by Art Weingarten and Gerald Sanford, 1968 August 21 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Includes daily production reports.
    - A FEW KIND WORDS FOR CHARLIE by Steffi and Tony Barrett, 1972 December 13 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - FEVER by Margaret and Paul Schneider, 1970 (Box 12, Folders 6-7)
    - A GIFT FOR JENNY by Gerald Sanford, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Working title: THE FUR COAT OF DEATH; also includes production documents.
    - THE HEALER by Gwen Bagni and Paul Dubov, 1969 (Box 13, Folders 2-3)
      Working title: THE QUACK. Also includes production documents.
    - I AM MY BROTHER'S KEEPER by James Schmerer, 1971 June 18 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - THE GURU by Leigh Chapman, 1968 May 6 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - GUESS WHO'S COMING TO MURDER by Jerome Ross, 1968 May 6 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - CAN YOU HEAR ME OUT THERE? by Stanley Ralph Ross, 1972 June 15 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - THE GIRL IN CHAIR NINE, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - GOOD TIMES ARE JUST MEMORIES by S.S. Schweitzer and Sandor Stern, from a story by Richard Buell and S.S. Schweitzer, 1972 May 10 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - IS THAT JUSTICE? by David H. Vowell, 1970 December 9 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - IN THIS CORNER -- SOL ALPERT by Rita Lakin and Harve Bennett, 1969 September 25 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - THE HOT HOT CAR by Elroy Schwartz, 1970 (Box 14, Folders 3-4)
    - A HINT OF DARKNESS, A HINT OF LIGHT by Edward J. Lakso, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - A GIRL'S BEST FRIEND by Gwen Bagni and Paul Dubov, 1968 (Box 14, Folders 6-7)
    - JUST RING THE BELL ONCE by Gwen Bagni and Paul Dubov, 1970 April 6 (Box 15, Folders 1-3)
    - THE JUDAS TRAP by Walter Black, from a story by Walter Black & Alvin Boretz, 1970 October 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - JIGSAW by Rick Husky, 1971 (Box 15, Folders 5-6)
    - IS THERE ANYONE LEFT IN SANTA PAULA? by Gene L. Coon, 1970 (Box 15, Folders 7-8)
    - KRISTIE by Rick Husky, 1972 (Box 16, Folders 1-2)
    - THE KING OF EMPTY CUPS by Sonya Roberts, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - KILL GENTLY, SWEET JESSIE by Steffi and Tony Barrett, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - KICKS, INCORPORATED by Peggy O'Shea, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - KEEP THE FAITH, BABY by Harve Bennett, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - LAUGHTER OF FOOLS by Edward J. Lasko, 1970 (Box 17, Folders 1-2)
    - LISA by Steffi and Tony Barrett, 1969 (Box 17, Folders 3-6)
    - MY NAME IS MANOLETE by Margaret Armen, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - THE MOTHER OF SORROW by William Wood and Rita Lakin, 1969 (Box 18, Folders 2-3)
    - LOVE by Henry Rosenbaum, 1968 September 3 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - THE LOSER by Sheldon Stark, 1970 (Box 18, Folders 5-6)
      Also includes production documents. Working title: THE OUTCAST.
    - THE NIGHT HOLDS TERROR by Rick Husky, 1972 (Box 19, Folders 1-3)
    - NEVER GIVE THE FUZZ AN EVEN BREAK by Malvin Wald, 1969 (Box 19, Folders 4-5)
    - MY, WHAT A PRETTY BUS by Gwen Bagni and Paul Dubov, 1968 (Box 19, Folders 6-7)
      Also includes Standards and Practices review.
    - THE POISONED MIND by Ernie Frankel, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - A PLACE TO RUN, A HEART TO HIDE IN by Edward J. Lasko, 1969 May 19 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - PIGEON WITH A BROKEN WING by S.S. Schweitzer, 1971 June 4 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - WILLIE POOR BOY by Richard Landau, 1969 (Box 20, Folders 4-5)
    - PEACE NOW -- ARLY BLAU!, 1969 February 26 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - ONCE MORE, WITH STEALING... by Jack Turley, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - THE PRICE OF TERROR by Tony Barrett, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      Also includes shooting schedule.
    - PUT OUT THE WELCOME MAT FOR DEATH by Elroy Schwartz, 1972 June 13 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - THE PRICE OF LOVE by Tony Barrett and Robert Foster, 1971 (Box 21, Folders 3-5)
    - THE POISONED MIND by Ernie Frankel, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - A RUN FOR THE MONEY by Edward J. Lasko, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - ROPE'S END by Richard Landau, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - RIDE THE MAN DOWN, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - RETURN TO DARKNESS, RETURN TO LIGHT by Edward J. Lasko, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - A REIGN OF GUNS by Tony Barrett from a story by Dan Ullman, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - A QUIET WEEKEND IN THE COUNTRY by Tony Barrett from a story by Jackson Gillis, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - A REIGN OF GUNS by Tony Barrett from a story by Dan Ullman, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - SEARCH AND DESTROY by David P. Harmon, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - SCION OF DEATH by Skip Webster, 1972 November 9 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - THE SANDS OF ANGER by Edward J. Lasko, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folders 3-4)
    - RUN, LINCOLN, RUN! by Donald Stewart, 1972 October 18 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - SANCTUARY, 1972 (Box 23, Folders 6-7)
    - SHOULD AULD ACQUAINTANCE BE FORGOT by Rita Lakin and Harve Bennett from a story by Joel Hammil and Ed Lasko, 1970 February 8 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - SHOCKWAVE by Rick Husky, 1971 (Box 24, Folders 2-3)
    - SEE THE EAGLES DYING by Edward J. Lasko, 1970 (Box 24, Folders 4-5)
    - A SEAT BY THE WINDOW by Edward J. Lasko, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - SUFFER, LITTLE CHILDREN by Gene L. Coon, 1970 (Box 25, Folders 1-2)
    - THE SONG OF WILLIE by Steffi and Tony Barrett, 1970 (Box 25, Folders 3-4)
    - A SILENT MAJORITY OF ONE by Robert Foster, 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 5-6)
    - TAPS, PLAY IT LOUDER by Sandor Stern, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - THE TANGLED WEB by Ernest Frankel, 1971 (Box 26, Folders 2-3)
    - SWEET CHILD OF TERROR by Edward J. Lasko, 1969 October 16 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      Includes production material.
    - SURVIVAL by Walter Black from a story by Elroy Schwartz and Walter Black, 1971 May 14 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      Includes call sheets.
    - SURVIVAL HOUSE by Joanna Lee and Harve Bennett, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - THE THUNDER MAKERS by Jack Turley, 1972 (Box 27, Folders 1-2)
    - THE TEETH OF THE BARRACUDA by Tony Barrett, 1967 (Box 27, Folders 3-5)
    - THE TWAIN by Skip Webster, 1972 September 28 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - A TOWN CALLED SINCERE by Gwen Bagni and Paul Dubov, 1969 (Box 28, Folders 2-3)
    - TO LINC -- WITH LOVE by Carol Sobieski, 1969 July 3 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - A TIME FOR REMEMBERING by Harve Bennett, 1970 January 12 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - A TIME OF HYACINTHS, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - A TIME TO LOVE -- A TIME TO CRY by Stephen Kandel, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      Former title: MY FRIEND, MY MURDERER.
    - THE UPTIGHT TOWN, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Includes Standards and Practices review. Former title: TOWN IN A TRAP.
    - WELCOME TO THE HUMAN RACE, LEVI FRAZEE! by Walter Black, 1970 June 5 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - WELCOME TO OUR CITY by Shirl Hendryx and Tony Barrett from a story by Shirl Hendryx, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folders 3-5)
    - TWINKLE, TWINKLE, LITTLE STARLET by Jerome Ross, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - YESTERDAY'S ASHES by Skip Webster, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - WHEN SMITTY COMES MARCHING HOME by Tony Barrett and Harve Bennett, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - WHO ARE THE KEEPERS, WHO ARE THE INMATES? by Richard Landau, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - WE SPY by Walter Black and Harve Bennett, 1971 January 23; 19 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - WHO ARE THE KEEPERS, WHO ARE THE INMATES? by Richard Landau, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - YOU CAN'T TELL THE PLAYERS WITHOUT A PROGRAMMER, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - ANOTHER FINAL GAME by Frank Telford, 1972 July 28 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - CORBEY by Jack Turley, 1972 August 17 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - YESTERDAY'S ASHES by Skip Webster, 1972 June 30 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - THE FUR COAT OF DEATH by Gerald Sanford, 1972 July 10 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - GOOD TIMES ARE JUST MEMORIES by S.S. Schweitzer and Sandor Stern from a story by Richard Bluell and S.S. Schweitzer, 1972 May 10 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - EYES OF THE BEHOLDER by Steffi and Tony Barrett, 1972 May 31 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - TAPS, PLAY IT LOUDER by Sandor Stern, 1972 June 20 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - SANCTUARY by Robert Hamner, 1972 June 12 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - THE LOSER by Robert C. Dennis, 1971 June 2 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - EXIT THE CLOSER by Robert Collins, 1971 July 10 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - KRISTIE by Rick Husky, 1972 October 4 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - CAN YOU HEAR ME OUT THERE? by Stanley Ralph Rose, 1972 August 3 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - RUN, LINCOLN, RUN! by Donald Stewart, 1972 October 18 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - THE TWAIN by Skip Webster, 1972 September 28 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - CRICKET by Rick Husky, 1971 July 28 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - JIGSAW by Rick Husky, 1971 August 31 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - BELINDA - THE END OF LITTLE MISS BUBBLEGUM by Bryn Morgan, 1972 September 12 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - PUT OUT THE WELCOME MAT FOR DEATH by Elroy Schwartz, 1972 November 2 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - THE CONNECTION by Rick Husky, 1972 May 4 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - THE THUNDER MAKERS by Jack Turley, 1972 April 20 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - THE TANGLED WEB by Ernest Frankel, 1971 December 21 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - THE CAVE by Don Ingalls, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - KILL GENTLY, SWEET JESSIE by Steffi and Tony Barrett, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - SHOCKWAVE by Rick Husky, 1971 November 11 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - FEET OF CLAY by Don Ingalls, 1971 October 4 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - I AM MY BROTHER'S KEEPER by James Schmerer, 1971 October 7 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - THE GURU by Leigh Chapman, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - LOVE by Henry Rosenbaum, 1968 August 23 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - CRIME CLUB by Theodore J. Flicker, 1972 April 27 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - CORBEY by Jack Turley, 1972 July 26 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - IS THERE ANYONE LEFT IN SANTA PAULA? by Gene L. Coon, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - FEVER by Margaret and Paul Schneider, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - FIND TARA CHAPMAN! treatment by Arthur Weingarten, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      Working title: WHO KNOWS ME HERE IN CHINA? Also includes breakdown for a Tony Lawrence script and a story idea from Jerry Ross.
    - HELLO MOTHER, MY NAME IS JULIE by Gwen Bagni and Paul Dubov, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - YOU CAN'T TELL THE PLAYERS WITHOUT A PROGRAMMER by Stephen Kandel, 1968 July 22 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - THE PRICE OF TERROR by Tony Barrett, 1968 August 13 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - TEETH OF THE BARRACUDA story by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
      Also includes: story idea by Don Ingalls; story "Who Are the Keepers - Who Are the Inmates" by Richard Landau; outline "Is There Anyone Left in Santa Paula?" by Gene L. Coon; outline "Suffer, Little Children" by Gene L. Coon; outline "Kristie" by Rick Husky; two outlines "Corbey" by Jack Turley; two stories "Child of a Child" by Margaret and Paul Schneider.
    - THE ACTIVIST by Mann Rubin, 1970 August 17 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - FLIGHT FIVE DOESN'T ANSWER by Harve Bennett from a story by Stephen Kandel, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - UNCLE VIC WANTS YOU outline by Ernie Frankel, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
      Also includes outline "The Mexican Bride" by Robert Lewin; story idea "And No Birds Sing" by Jameson Brewer; outline "Linc Returns to Watts" by Robert L. Goodwin; outline "Child of Sorrow, Child of Light" by Cliff Gould; outline "You Die in the Middle" by George Bellak; treatment "Helltown" by Edward J. Lasko.
    - DEATH IN HIGH PLACES outline by Robert Hamner, undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
      Also includes: outline "The Steel Zoo" by Richard Landau; story ideas from Ernie Frankel; submissions from Rick Husky; submissions from Don Ingalls; story "Murder in the Future Tense" by James Menzies; outline "The Treasure of the Back Room" by Theodore Apstein.
    - IF IT WEREN'T FOR THE MILKMAN outline by Felix Jackson, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
      Also includes: outline "The Shack" by Gene Nelson; outline "Life on the Flip Side" by Robert Hamner; outline "Too Much Too Soon" by Arthur C. Pierce; outline by Jerome Moss; treatment "Helltown" by Edward J. Lasko; outline "The Cruel Sky" by Dan Ullman.
    - DEATH IN HIGH PLACES by Robert Hamner, 1972 November 29 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - THE FOURTH MAN by Jack B. Sowards, 1972 (Box 38, Folders 1-2 and 5)
    - Story suggestion "Josie" by Alf Harris, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence regarding filming on the Queen Mary, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous documents, 1968-1970 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      Includes: shooting schedules; script status report; release schedule; report on test screenings.
    - Story outlines, 1967-1969 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      Includes: outline by Allan Sloane; "Bright Candle" by Sheldon Stark; ideas from John Kneubel; "Deathflight" by Edward J. Lasko; "The Plan"; jewel theft story by Gerald Sanford.
    - TEETH OF THE BARRACUDA additional pages, 1968-1969 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      Also includes: test screening report for WHEN SMITTY COMES MARCHING HOME; script status reports.
    - Story ideas, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      Includes: "The Thunder Makers" by Jack Turley; idea from Charles McDaniels; ideas "from A.S." (probably Aaron Spelling).
    - Story outlines, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      Includes:"Rope's End" by Richard Landau; "Crisscross."
    - Story outlines, 1068 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      Correspondents include Richard Zimbert, Aaron Spelling, and ABC, largely regarding finances.
    - Memos, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      Notes on stories and writers.
    - Story ideas, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Story ideas, circa 1973 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      Includes: ideas from Ed Lasko and Bert Mulligan; clippings; post-production status reports.
    - Story ideas, 1966-1972 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Post-production status reports, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Story ideas, circa 1968 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Black Feature idea, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Cost reports, 1968-1971 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Post-production status reports, 1972-1974 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      Also includes a "comprehensive report" on various NBC programs, 1974 January 28.
    - Credits, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Cost reports, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Shooting schedules, 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Shooting schedules, 1969-1972 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      Also includes schedule for television movie The Monk (ABC, 1969).
    - Department of Broadcast Standards and Practices, 1968-1972 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      Includes: report on "When Smitty Comes Marching Home"; offset of article "Television Violence" by Melvin S. Helle and Samuel Polsky; "The Television Code" of the National Association of Broadcasters, 1971 March.
    - Story ideas, circa 1972 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Production binder, 1969-1971 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      Includes: budgets; cost reports; broadcast and shooting schedules; WGA correspondence.
    - OH, SEE THE BEAUTIFUL PEOPLE by Don Ingalls and Margaret Armen, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - CRY UNCLE by Sandor Stern, 1972 December 22 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      Includes production documents. Also includes script for THE SUNDAY DRIVERS by Edward J. Lasko, 1968 October 21.
    - Production binder, 1968-1971 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      Includes: shooting schedules; cost reports; staff and crew lists.
    - Production binder, 1969-1972 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      Includes: script distribution lists; script status reports; cost reports; release schedules.
    - A FAVOR FOR A FRIEND by Tony Barrett, 1968 November 11 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      Also includes DEATH RACE by Edward J. Lasko, 1968 September 26.
    - SHELLGAME by Edward J. Lasko, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - THE SUNDAY DRIVERS by Edward J. Lasko, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - THE MEXICAN BRIDE by Robert Lewin, 1968 August 12 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Services, 1970-1971 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      Includes correspondence and brochures from various companies.
    - Production reports and schedules, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - 'TIL DEATH - OR MURDER - DO US PART by Robert Lewin, 1968 October 8 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - WILD WEEK-END by Jack Turley, 1971 August 6 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - AND ONCE FOR MY BABY by Robert Sherman, 1972 November 14 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - CHILD OF A CHILD by Margaret and Paul Schneider, 1972 October 23 (Box 43, Folder 3)